Seino! Hello! This is Shellshell! Yay!
It's started! The shish-kebab parley show!
Yay!
I've done a shish-kebab parley performance on Deshiko Akane Noda's YouTube channel.
The first part is on there.
There was a great battle!
It was a battle!
Not a parley, but a parley!
There was a fight in the parley, too.
If you haven't seen it yet, you can see it there and then come back here.
You can come back here.
I'm glad you're here.
Let's introduce ourselves again.
Yes!
Hello everyone, we are
I'm Akane Noda Deshiko.
I'm Suzuki Kawahara.
I'm Hina Nahoda.
I am Yurusa Higashiyama.
I am Naho Suzuki
I am Suzumi Suzu
I am Lili Haruna
I am Miho Hoshitani
I am Momona Matsumoto
I am Seri Kamiyama.
Shall we introduce ourselves too?
Yes!
Naho first.
I'm Nao Sakura, Dragon's Blue.
Yes, sir!
Purple Purple, I'm Oguro.
Yes!
Nagoya Red, I am Akimoto Ponaka.
I am Haruna Amido.
I'm Haruna Amido.
Don't you notice anything?
I did.
I heard.
I thought you were auditioning.
You were.
Last time we did this...
Who won?
Yes, I did.
These six won?
We've switched reds since last time.
You switched reds.
And...
Switch reds.
And then
Do the red change.
Switch red.
Do the red switch.
Do a red change
This time, we're going to wake up the theater.
And here we go again.
You guys want to win?
I want to win!
You wanna draw!
Then let's start the show over there!
Yes, sir!
Quick!
This way!
I can't wait to eat.
That was fast.
What are you going to eat?
I'm trying to decide which one to try, and I'm having trouble.
That's good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm scared.
Then I guess I'll have quail for the tasting.
Oh, quail.
Quail looks delicious.
Oh, yeah?
You sure?
I'll have this one.
Then let's have it all at once.
Bon appétit!
Ohhh...
What should I do?
Deliver it, deliver it!
Who's having dinner?
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's frustrating.
I'll go next time.
I don't know what I'll do.
Let's see.
In the first half, you know, a very moving scene.In the first half, you know, a great emotional scene.
A very moving scene.
I'd like to end on this impression.
Then the best of Cyanide, which I was wondering about.
I'll take it.
Oh!
I won!
Congratulations!
Well, I think I'll have the meat.
I think I'll have some meat.
Oh! I won!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes!
Surprisingly, isn't it amazing? That's the color right there.
Is this the winner?
Is it going to be a big hit?
Well, in that case, I'll take that one.
This one?
I got them all.
Oh, my God.
Onions?
Well, I'm not an onion person, so...
Maybe he likes onions.
What are these?
Potatoes?
Okay, let's go to meat.
So far, the meat ratio is pretty high, isn't it? I think so.
Oh, really?
You're keeping statistics?
Okay, let's go!
Wow!
I was right!
I'm so sorry.
Congratulations!
Thank you for your hard work.
Please pull your help.
Yes, sir.
What do we get?
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
Yes.
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
Next...
What?
What is it?
Come on, come on!
It's too early! It's early!
Come on!
Red change!
Too soon!
Isn't it too early?
Okay, so the red change is complete.
Yuzuki, you go that way...
I'm going to eat!
What?
I haven't said anything yet.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I'm coming over there!
What the fuck?
Screaming.
Why!
Nao is going to eat Yuzuki's portion again.
How is this possible?
Oh no, we were spared!
We got away with it, didn't we?
Chicken?
I'll take mine.
Then it's onions.
Onions.
I don't know what I'd feel if it was onions.
Bon appétit!
Gukkoi.
Ah!
Bingo!
Oh!
Ooh!
Bye, Saki.
Which one shall we eat?
Let's eat.
Shin-chan didn't put much in the gift box last time.
That's true.
Gift for you...
I got a gift for you.
That's nice.
It's nice.
He's my son's.
Oh, my son's son?
Yes...
Well, what should we eat?
Well, I'll at least have some shrimp.Then I'll at least have some shrimp.
I'd like that.
I'll have some shrimp.
I like it.
Yes, I'll have some shrimp.
Fifteen.
Fifteen?
I'm 15.
Uh-huh.
Yes, sir.
I'll at least have a shrimp.
Here you go.
Wow!
Bingo!
It's okay. That's great.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's OK! Oki.
Oki. Okay.
Let's see what you got.
Three, two, one.
Ahhh...
Aaaaah!
What's coming out?
It's done.
Here it is.
Expectation complete.
Yay!
You want to go tell him it's your birthday? Okay, then.
May 28th.
Yes!
July 18th.
August 22.
September 10.
Oh!
December 12. oh!
October 30.
Uh-oh.
November 5.
November 15.
December 25.
January 16.
February 2.
March 3.
March 22.
There you go again.
Hime-chan, are you there?
What's that?
She's always been here.
I can't eat forever.
It's cold.
See you later.
After Nau?
After who?
After the first one?
See you.
We don't even know if this one's here.
They could both be red.
We can't eat the thorns again.
He's miserable.
I ate onions.
with this jaguar.
I'm pretty sure this is red.
Here we go.
Red.
Mr. Yusaku...
He said he'd give it to you.
He delivered it.
Thank you.
I'm scared.
I'm looking forward to it.
Have some shish-kebabs.
I'll do a full-on report.
Are you going to eat again?
You're going to eat again?
I'm going to eat so much!
I want to eat it!
I'll do my best.
I'll use the sweet potatoes I just pulled.
Bon appétit!
I'm serious, I'm serious!
Thank you for your hard work.
- How did you get it? I'm just lying, that's all.
Are there fewer and fewer corners to hit, first time around?
- What do you want?
- I heard it's a high meat count. I'd like to serve it here.
- He's pretty cool.
He's pretty cool.
He's so hot. - He's so hot! - Car rush!
- I'm scared.
- Wow!
- I hit it!
- Yes, you're right. I'll start from here.
- From here!
- It starts from here.- It's from here.
- TOMMY SCHOOL 530!!!
- Yeah!
- Okay!
- Yay!
- Yeah!
- Do you want to count down? How do you want to start?
- Where do you want me to start?
- Guess.
- Guess. Kurtz.
- Kurtz. You're gonna die.
- You're gonna die. I'm worried.
- I'll eat it.
- Wow!
You did it!
Come on!
Let's go to Starbucks on this trend!
What's that?
High tension mimicry
High-tension mimicry.
It's so hard.
Who wrote this?
It's true.
Mike.
You buy it with a microphone?
Mike's.
Do you have a box or something?
I'm just doing my impersonations.
I'm excited, too, Momochan.
Okay, then...
I'm not here, but can I do Momoko Hashimoto's impersonation?
I'll do it.
Hello everyone! I'm Momoko Hashimoto!
Are you here today?
I love you so much!
Don't you like Momoko?
I love Momoko though!
She said it!
How many more?
Two.
Is this all of them?
Yeah.
Cute!
Let's try some.
It's good, right?
Together?
They're both good.
What is this?
Can you eat it?
Are you sure you're okay?
Make sure it's on.
I'll make it a long course.
You want to join us?
Oh, my God!
What?
That's not red?
It's not red?
Isn't that red on your hand?
Red!
Yes!
No, no, no.
Here you go.
Go downstairs and play piano-nick.
There you go.
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Yay!
My Melo.
Ah!
High tension maimelo!
It's hard to see
Here we go.
High Tension Maimelo, here you go!
I'm My Melo.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm a mymelo, ha-ha-ha-ha-ha...
That's all I've got.
I'll do my best
I'm a little broken.
I'm broken.
I'm broken
It's broken.
Did it hurt?
It hurts.
Don't say that again.
Do you want me to say it again?
What?
It's okay.
I wanted to.I wanted to.
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
I wanted to.
I want them to do it.
Okay.
You two want to go?
I'll go with you.
You don't know if I'm in it.
I don't know if you're in it.
Do you want to open it together?
Let's see what's in there.
Call me in.
Here it is.
Let's see.
Ready?
Dong!
Wow.
I can get the member with the face I like.
Time to have the skewers unleashed.
What?
Why don't you just have fries?
Serious confession time for the camera
Time for serious confessions for the camera!
I did it!
I've been waiting for it.
You know, we could do this together.
I wonder if we can.
Sure.
Maybe we can do it together.
What?
You're going to do Anne in confession?
With your distinctive voice.
I'm sure.
I mean it.
Very distinctive.
Are you two ready?
Let's start with a confession of love.
Anne.
When you sat next to me today, the moment you smiled at me.
I fell in love with you.
If you don't mind, will you go out with me?
I beg you.
Yay!
Can I have a special treat?
Can I?
Is that it?
I've never done that before.
It's my first time. I'll do it.
Please do.
I look forward to working with you for many years to come.
Team Shachia.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, no!
Welcome back.
Oh no!
Cheese crunchy!
What's that?
He's got me from above!
Crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
Cheese crunchy!
You made some great memories!
I'm looking forward to the show.
I'm sure you are.
It's hard to believe it's our first time together.
We're so close.
We got to know each other so well.
Watching this video, I think we were able to get to know each other on a personal level.
I think everyone was able to get to know each other.
I would like to ask you to watch each other's music videos
I hope you will see each other's music videos
and listen to each other's songs
I'm sure you'll get excited about our live performance.
I think it will be a lot of fun.
Don't you think it'll be exciting?
Yes, I do.
So, Takamiko's tour
June 18th at Nagoya Park
at Bottom Line, so please come and join us!
Please come and join us!
I look forward to seeing you there!
That's all for now.
This is Team Shaki and Ms. Takamiko.
Bye bye!